Is that the reason why the two of you wouldn't let me see you work this whole time?
Come on, you should have told me.
Hello, Officer Chun? Did you catch him yet? Did he say anything about my friend?
Well, we matched the license plate, but it's no good. He isn't our guy.
That can't be right. You saw one of the victims getting into that car, did you not?
It's Emma from Trader Games. It's clear the two of them are connected. I'll figure it out.
How do you know all that? Is someone leaking you info? Here's the deal.
So they get him? What's up?
No, not yet at least.
Why not? What are they doing?
Liu Min couldn't have killed that woman. We have the proof. It'd be impossible.
That can't be!
Yeah, Liu Min was in the hospital whenever she died.
Plus, we found footage of her that night. Walking alone on an old bridge.
You can go ahead and send me your friend's information. It's too early to call her missing, though.
Even if it hasn't been 48 hours yet, we'll still keep an eye out.
Right. Thank you.
Okay. So what's the plan?
We can't file a report. We're on our own for now.
It didn't take too long to realize
Something has changed in the back of my mind
Your eyes
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind
Time no longer flew like it was
When the flash froze everything before
Without you
I don't know if I could take this road
And I'm about to lose my mind
Every minute that I die back in time
Every single existence rewinds
Some physical pain in this eye dry
All mine
All the heartaches and the smiles never faded
I know you'll be by my side when we make it
Come back from the times
Back in time
Die back in time
I didn't want to have to deal with your kind, but oh well.
Spit it out! Now! Where's my money?
Please, please let me go. I'm sorry. I don't know what money you're talking about.
No? Let me refresh your memory!
Well, we have to do something.
Hi, Dongyi.
Hey, do you know what Shan Shan might be doing now? Her phone is turned off.
I don't know. She's so flighty. Bet she forgot to plug it in and the battery died.
Yeah, you're right. Guess I'll just try her again later.
We're sorry. The number you've dialed cannot be reached.
It's no good. Take a look at this. She could be hurt, and we're just standing around.
Where did the two of you go yesterday? When did you get home?
We grabbed milk tea then. That was about it. I think I got back around. I'm not sure.
Wait. Did she take any photos after she left here? Selfies? Anything that would help us?
No. I don't think so.
Then what about before? Did she text you any pics yesterday?
Um, let me look and see. She may have.
Anything in the last 12 hours?
We didn't talk much after we said goodbye. Most of these are from days ago.
Keep looking, just in case you missed something while you were scrolling through.
I am, but everything I have saved is older.
Here. What about this? Did she take it yesterday?
Oh, that's right. Before we entered the shop, I think she had her phone out.
And if that's the case, then that photo should work, right?
Quick, do it. Maybe you can find a clue.
What?
Okay.
I don't know.
What is it?
What did you see?
Last night at 1.30, somebody broke into her place and then he attacked her.
I need to dive in! We have to save her right now!
Hold on. Are you certain you're prepared to go through this?
Even if we relive what happened after she took the photo, nothing can change. Those are the rules.
My connection was broken when the masked man lunged at her. It's likely she didn't survive.
If that's really the case, then he would experience her death while inside of her body, knowing the whole time that he can't save her.
Give him some time to think.
Let them all leave. You're not allowed to go anywhere, understand?
Listen, there's something I've been meaning to tell you for a while.
We're sorry. The number you dialed cannot be reached.
There you are. I hope nothing's wrong. The interviewer was asking for you.
Oh, right. Something came up. I'll head in later.
Yeah. By then, it'll be over.
We're sorry. The number you dialed cannot be reached.
Not be reached.
Captain Shell, we've confirmed with Liu Min's doctors. He is indeed paralyzed.
Here's the thing. I'm at your friend's place, but I can't do much since nobody's answering the door.
Right. Thanks for stopping by anyway.
So, you decide?
I'm ready to dive.
What are you doing? Come on! You look great!
Whoa! Little too close. You're making me feel weird.
Control yourself and stay in character, please.
Stop joking around. Your answers await.
Look who I brought!
Hey, favorite landlady.
A guest has arrived.
Shouldn't you be off studying to be a doctor or something?
What? So I'm just supposed to treat myself like an idiot?
You knew what this was. Start talking.
Uh, I dropped by because I heard you need more work. Uh, something about debt?
I see. Slumming it with the idiots, are ya?
You're too kind.
So then, Miss Scholar, going crazy?
I had to stay in school. Unlike someone I know, I don't want to rely on others for handouts.
Will you please try to stay focused? Nobody in the world argues that nonchalantly.
Hey now! You got it wrong!
I play a vital role!
Here!
Blaine put a roof over your head and Lu Guang manages the business while you coast along making jokes!
We are partners!
Didn't anyone ever teach you not to talk crap if you don't have all the facts?
I'm back!
Mr. Liu, your room has been cleaned. I'll head out now.
Damn it! Why won't they leave me alone?
You're all trash and need to be slaughtered!
If this girl wants to be famous so badly, I'll grant her wish. What do you think, my dear friend?
Idiot! Shoulda hit him harder.
Hey, so I know they need photos, but how do they get info from them?
I wish I knew the answer to that. They won't let anyone see them work. It really is a mystery.
Yeah. In that case, I'm not gonna hold my breath. That loud mouth might do something stupid.
Ain't that the truth.
Nah. He's a tool. Lu's the one in charge here. I can assure you he's reliable. You're in good hands.
A tool? Seriously? You really think that's the truth?
Yeah, now that I think about it, that makes perfect sense to me.
I'm hard on him, but the truth is our resident loud mouth truly does have a tenacious spirit,
even if it is deep down inside. He pretends not to, but I know that isn't the case. When we were younger,
he was like that too.
I don't get it. How could any parent just leave their kid behind like this?
I know. It's terrible. What did they expect he'd do here without them?
We could take turns caring for him.
Please.
I'm not sure how it would be wise.
Not me. Always a chance they're still alive. Maybe stuck somewhere.
I should call the police first. They'll know what to do.
Stop talking! My parents just went on a trip. They're going to come back.
I'm not going anywhere. And I don't want your sympathy. Get out of here! All of you!
I'm grateful, kid. We were just trying to help.
Oh, so rude. The nerve of this boy. Come on, let's go.
What about you? Do you think my parents abandoned me too?
I'm sure they'll come back soon. Can I wait with you?
Yeah, sure. And thank you.
Don't thank me. Thank my dad. He said he'll lend you 10 years' rent.
Then when you grow up, you can open the shop again and pay him back.
Oh, I guess that means I'll have to start calling you my landlady.
We tried our best to help him back then, but he had a hard time.
He seemed so resilient, doing his best to fit in with the other kids and pretending he wasn't hurt.
But it wore on him every day.
People weren't kind to him.
The noobs. There was a big earthquake. He killed a bunch of people last night and died.
I don't know what to do. Were my mom and dad caught in it?
What if they don't come back? What if I never see them again?
Don't you worry. They were probably nowhere near that disaster. I'm sure they'll come back home.
What if they're both dead and now I'm all alone? I miss them already.
I miss them so much.
He was in so much pain. I can't imagine. But he put up such a strong front.
Never wanting our pity.
I always worried he wouldn't be able to make new friends that actually cared about him.
And then…
Hey, it's you.
Oh, Lou!
Hmm? Who's this guy? Is he… a friend?
Just passing by.
Hey, wait. If you're free, we could use another hand.
Lou appeared in our lives like a miracle.
I distinctly remember asking him how they became friends in the first place.
Can you guess what he said?
Was he attracted to his dashing good looks?
As if.
I'm gonna grab a sodas.
Cool. Diet for me.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, what do you like about this doofus anyway?
The two of us go way back. And you're the first new friend I've met in all these years.
He asked me to play basketball. And I had a good time.
So you went from sports buddies to pals, which tells me there must be some reason you stuck around.
Care to share details?
It's cause… he's genuine?
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
Lou was being serious. And honestly, I have to agree with him.
Cheng Xiaoshi has such an open, innocent heart. It makes you want to protect him.
Thanks. That's kind of you.
Why are you thanking me? You're being so strange today.
Whatever. It's boba time. I'm so excited.
Shouldn't we be grabbing dinner instead?
This'll be our dinner. It's less calories.
Sir, you've been loitering around here the whole day.
Come to apologize to a girlfriend or something?
We've all been in that boat before.
Well, honestly, I'm not sure if we're dating.
I'm waiting to find out.
20 minutes until the incident.
Well, are you prepared?
I got this.
When you go looking for the murderer, you'll find him hiding in the bathroom.
That'll be your best chance to unmask him.
Hey, Lou.
I want you to trust me to take the lead this time.
What? Why should I?
Here we are.
You're pretty punctual.
But I can't let that happen.
I've got a proposition.
Let's play a game.
I'll send you a clue.
You'll get it at 10 a.m.
Where's my phone?
Tomorrow at this time, find the real me.
Interesting.
If I win, will you promise to be my new friend?
Leave this girl alone, and I won't call the cops, okay?
I've locked him inside.
Great.
The games...
Over it.
看وا ہے.
I saw you, but the phone didn't play.
It's got a true.
It's just to give me a call on you.
Right.
That the typical lightzan?
What is it now belongs to me?
In fact, I know I want to wrap you up in your face.
酒杯梦念这分钟里漂浮
我可是能够回到中间 在这边的光潮四四摇住
就像变的机会 还满在我小骨子里
这若干年过去了 我是否还能做我自己
I got lost in the street that I'm living in
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking
我一时看了看我的右手
那落叶掠过了我的胸口
没来得及手藏着天后
我目光怎么又被偷走
You should really stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
While your mind overclouded
脱离现实的梦境化危机
时钟的我需要怎样才能自保
So stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
While your mind overclouded
在这时间的缝隙停着思考
我明白多少烦恼都是永远自容
Stop thinking about it
I want you stop stop thinking about it
While your mind overclouded